James Han

jameshan044@gmail.com Canada, Manseau QC

SUMMARY

Full stack developer with over 8+ years of experience in Java/JS, Angular, Vue, React, Python, Node.js. In improving user engagement by 15%, reducing development and deployment time by 20% and mentoring junior developers, resulting in a 10% improvement in team satisfaction scores. I have also good experience of temworks.

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

HubSpot 2020 - 2023

HubSpot is a leading inbound marketing and sales software company headquartered in Cambridge, Massachusetts, USA. Founded in 2006 by Brian Halligan and Dharmesh Shah.

- Engineered a membership platform from scratch using MERN; increased retention rate by 5% and saved the company 10 hours of manual work per week
- · Researched and created a new application to be used by the company, resulting in a 1.24x increase in sales
- Generated \$50K+ in annual ad revenue as a system administrator of a large network of websites.
- Developed a node.js server to validate membership and track digital badges being used, saving the company \$22.5K.
- · Mentored 4 team members, enabling them to achieve professional growth and personal goals
- Developed the process of testing and recording the results of the test, thereby increasing the number of tests completed per day by 10%
- Developed a new technique for reducing the time it takes to fix crashes by 20%

Full Stack Developer

Los Angeles, California

Mezzanine 2017 - 2020

Mezzanine is a California-based company that specializes in providing innovative solutions for businesses. They offer a wide range of services, including software development, web design, digital marketing, and IT consulting.

- Fostered a culture of collaboration within the team by implementing agile methodologies, leading to a 10% increase in project efficiency and a 5% reduction in time-to-market
- Designing a new web application to enhance collaboration between design, engineering and sales teams increased revenue by 10% in one quarter.
- · Built a custom web application for a major client, successfully delivering an integrated CRM system in just 2 weeks
- Conceptualized, designed, and produced 50+ digital and print marketing materials using Adobe InDesign and Illustrator; increased website traffic by 15%, and sales by 5% in 6 months

Junior Web Developer

New York, New York

Fareportal

2014 - 2017

Fareportal is a leading travel technology company that operates a number of websites which serve customers both online and with telephone.

- Designed and implemented a new cloud-based mobile POS platform, resulting in a 2.5% increase in customer retention
- Coordinated cross-functional teams of hardware and software developers to ensure seamless integration of the new POS system; achieved 10% reduction in transaction processing time
- · Continued to develop specialty skills related to his expertise in mobile POS and payment technologies
- · Developed and continuously improved an internal knowledge base of best practices for software development

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Software Engineer

Hong Kong University of Science and Technology-Hong Kong

2010 - 2014

SKILLS

Web: MERN, JavaScript/TypeScript, HTML, CSS, Django, VueJs, AngularJs

Application: C/C++, Java, Python, Matlab, Android, Agile, Adobe InDesign, Docker, Firebase

Database: MongoDB, MySQL, Oracle